sometrics.com 2013-09-01

# Sometrics | Privacy Policy

  1. This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 1, 2011 and applies only to the website located at [www.sometrics.com](http://www.sometrics.com/).

We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party, including but not limited to our customers and clients, and any website or service that links to or from our website or Services.

Sometrics, Inc. ("Sometrics, Inc.", "we" or "us") is committed to your online privacy and protecting any and all personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") about you that we may collect and store as a result of our business activities with you. This Privacy Policy (this "Policy") outlines the type of information we may collect, how we might use such information, and the choices you have regarding such information.

We encourage you to read this Policy carefully. If you have any questions about this Policy, our use of your Personal Information, or your dealings with this website, please feel free to contact us by submitting a support request to us at [support@sometrics.com](mailto:support@sometrics.com)

. 

We may update this Policy from time to time in our sole discretion so please check back frequently. Any changes made to this Policy will be reflected in an updated policy (denoted by an updated date above) posted on our website at [www.sometrics.com](http://www.sometrics.com/). Your use of the website or Services after an updated policy has been posted will constitute your agreement to the Policy�s terms.

  2. ## Collection of Personal Information

Customers who use the products and services available through our website (collectively, the “Services”) and provide Personal Information to us, do so voluntarily. This information may include your name, contact information, and account-related information, which may also be linked to the types of payment options you may use, the types of ads you interact with, and information such as your IP-address or your browser. By allowing us to gather Personal Information, users are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of such Personal Information in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy.

  3. ## How We Use Personal Information

Any Personal Information collected and stored by us is used to provide the Services to you, for example, to improve the performance and usability of our Services, provide a better experience for you, as well as report to and from our business partners about any transactions or offers completed via our system, and to communicate directly with you Sometrics, Inc. does not share any customer Personal Information with any third party except as set forth in this Policy.

Sometrics, Inc. reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information without notice or consent as it deems necessary (a) to conform to applicable law; (b) when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and property; (c) to protect the safety of our users, us, or other third parties; (d) to comply with any judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us; and/or (e) pursuant to an acquisition, merger, sale of assets or other business transfer, bankruptcy, or dissolution.

  4. ## Log Files and Website Cookies

By accessing our website, our internet servers automatically record information that your internet browser sends when you visit a website. These logs may contain information such as your internet protocol (IP) address, browser version, domain name, language, date and time, the referring website and information in your cookie files. The foregoing is anonymous information that does not contain any Personal Information about you. We use this information to improve our website and Services.

Sometrics, Inc. (or our service providers) may place a temporary or persistent "cookie" on your computer's hard drive for purposes of (1) allowing our customers the convenience of not having to remember their login information when accessing our website, (2) gathering and aggregating statistical data about the usage of our website and Services for customers, and (3) sending targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you. Cookies are simple, harmless text files that remember the internet browser you use to access the internet. These cookies do not track, retain, or store any Personal Information, and they are used to gather the same general internet information that is available to all internet service providers, search engines, and websites. Examples of this information include, without limitation, a visitor's general location based on IP address, information from the visitor's browser such as browser type, type of operating system, keywords used while searching, websites visited, monitor resolution settings. If you do not want to receive cookies (and thereby, stop the foregoing anonymous information from being tracked), you may adjust the settings in your internet browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a website is attempting to place a cookie on your computer.

  5. ## Your Choices Regarding Information

You can opt-out of having your Personal Information used for email communications by selecting the opt-out option at the bottom of the email.

You can also stop Cookies (see above) from being stored on your computer and from being used for the purposes listed above, including for targeted advertising purposes. Most Internet browsers offer robust options in relation to cookies. The default settings in all major browsers accept cookies. However, by adjusting your browser settings, you can choose to automatically block cookies from specific web sites, from all web sites, from web sites without a privacy policy, or from all third parties. Consult the help manual for your browser for detailed information. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict Cookies, but later you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to restrict Cookies on that device as well. Deleting a Cookie does not mean you will no longer see online advertising; it does mean that Sometrics will not be able to target an advertisement to you based on information derived from the Cookie.

*Please note that blocking Cookies may interfere with your ability to access or use certain features of our website and Services.

If you have any other questions, please contact us (see below).

  6. ## Children's Data

We do not knowingly solicit or collect any personally identifiable information belonging to children under the age of 13. Our products and services are not directed to children under the age of 13. No one under the age of 13 is authorized to provide any personally identifiable information to us, to use our Services, or to engage in any transaction with us. if you believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided information to us, please contact us immediately (see below). 

  7. ## Data Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information collected by us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

  8. ## Contact

If you have questions or concerns regarding the Sometrics privacy policy please contact us at [support@sometrics.com](mailto:support@sometrics.com).

Our postal address is:  
Sometrics Inc.  
909 N Sepulveda Blvd, Suite 860  
El Segundo, CA 90245
